I'm on a journey out to see the world.
While I'm on my own, I've
yet to reach the end.
So won't you come along with me right now?
Surely then we can!
Follow me now as we
journey on from sea to sea.
For that treasure known
by everybody as one piece.
Even though they laugh and
say it's just a fantasy.
We are going, there's no doubt we go.
Cause we can feel the
rush of energy overcome.
It will lead the way.
Keep pretending that you know what to do.
Books will only get in the way.
No guides for today.
Do not worry, soon the rain
will be gone with the wind.
Keep your chin up, raise the
anchor, now that's what you'll do.
Give it time and calm the storm
that you have built within.
Come and have my board at number two.
Once tomorrow's wind picks up,
we set self cause we can't.
Thresh enough, stand tall and
take a look at one of you.
All the journey makes
me wanna see somebody.
There are things out there
you just won't believe.
Beyond your wildest dreams.
Don't think for a second.
It's not the truth.
That's the story.
Most will believe.
Not me.
Come and see.
I am on a journey.
Out to see the world.
Don't all of my own.
I've got my group of friends.
Together we've got our way.
That's how it's done.
Says your captain.
Who says it can't be done.
We haven't even tried.
Gotta just believe we'll
make it to the end.
I just wanna do it all right now.
Together surely we can.
Yes, we can.
You can.
Just take this moment in.
We can.
I can.
Just take this feeling in.
Right now.
Oh yes, we can.
Yes, we can!
Edgy? Correct.
That's the sound that
Race makes when he runs.
Just another one of his many skills.
It's ninpo.
Blindfolding technique.
Now, guess who?
It's Kanjado, of course.
There's no one else behind me.
Hit the door!
Oh, you trickster, you!
He fell off!
What do we do now?
What was that thing, and why the
heck was it falling out of the sky?
I'm not sure.
At first glance,
it looked like a wounded man covered
in blood and riddled with knives.
Or a little monkey.
You could have led with the
less gruesome one, you know!
Are you alive?
Say something back, are you alive?
Say something back—did they hit the water?
Let's save them, sir!
Loopy, not to worry—we are both unharmed!
Oh, that was kidding!
On, thank goodness—they're all right!
Please go on ahead—we'll reunite both!
Well, no way—is he crazy?
Let's turn around the
dragon—we need to go back!
Down—no other way! Hey,
turn around—he seems like he
wants to finish what
he
started!
No matter what he's
suffering—the better press on!
So cute!
what he's suffering the
better press on so cute
Okay, we're going on ahead!
We'll see you guys there!
A valiant choice! Halt!
You're not welcome in
that country! Proceed!
Whoever that other guy is, he's not happy.
Stay strong, Ryunosuke!
You can do it.
Ouch!
I see the top!
Wow, we're so close!
You're in the home stretch now, big guy!
Sweet!
Let's head to the top!
Come on!
Big sprint to the finish line!
Hey look!
I can see something!
A few more steps and we're there! Yeah!
Yeah!
Reunosuke!
Be strong, Reunosuke.
Reunosuke! Reunosuke!
Reunosuke!
Eee?
We made it!
We're here!
We finally reached the top!
Reunosuke!
It's all thanks to you!
We're on phone! Yeah!
Oh dear, you're changing back.
No, hold on!
Ryunosuke!
Ryunosuke! Don't go!
It's just a crappy drawing show.
Some respect, you jerks!
You can at least thank him
for bringing you all this way.
We don't know this place well.
Let's stay alert.
I mean, yeah, you're not wrong? but I...
Hey, Usopp, Ryunosuke was great, huh?
Never stop looking ahead. See that?
Must be the gate to the country.
Guess there really is a civilization
on this elephant's back.
They have a watchtower, but no guards.
Seems suspiciously undermanned.
Old business, aren't ya?
How did you guys get over our
friend's death so quickly?
Jeez.
Usopp, get up here real quick
We can check out the view!
That's easier said than done!
After all that hard work, we're here!
We made it to ZO!
Whoa!
How is this real?
Now that we're up here, it's
just like any other country.
You're right.
The whole thing is totally crazy.
Can you believe that elephant's
a thousand years old?
Let's explore. Come on.
It'll be a blast. Uh-huh.
There's a forest and a
river and a town, too.
Yeah, it goes on as far
as the eye can see. Look!
That tree is shaped like a whale!
Whoa, it is!
That town is bigger than I thought!
Uh?
Wait, there's something
off about it, though.
Yeah!
Ah, there he goes again!
Typical.
You see curly brows?
Nope, I'm too high up to see anyone!
Zoro, should we wait
here for the other two?
Nah, this place isn't that big.
They'll find us.
Don't just run off.
I'm coming too.
Why'd he jump the gates wide open?
That's not how I'd describe it.
Yeah, it was destroyed by force.
See, they plowed right through
it.
Not just that.
Look at the trail too.
No normal animal could
have made a path this wide.
You're right, man.
This is some next-level destruction.
It's still fresh, too.
Hope Sanji's group's okay.
Huh? What the heck?
It didn't look like this
from the watchtower.
What could have made this mess?
Only one way to find out.
We haven't even met the people here.
We've already got some
monster to worry about.
Wait, slow down.
If you guys would listen to me once in
a while and run away from the bad stuff,
our lives would be a lot better.
This is hard to walk on.
Yeah, it's elephant skin.
The flowers here grow in odd places.
What happened to Part?
The lesser minks waltz
right through the gate.
Maybe they beat him.
Whoa, this feels so weird!
It's really soft under your feet!
Here's the town!
There's tons of buildings,
but I don't see anybody!
Where are all the people?
Hey, Sanji, Nami, Chopper, Brock, Momo,
are any of you guys around? Where are you?
Come on, answer me! Hello?
Whoops, I forgot the gas guy again.
Jeez, what happened here?
Is that gunpowder I'm smelling?
Yeah, and a little bit of gas, too.
Oh, great.
More trouble.
Can't we just go to a peaceful
island once in a while?
I mean, really.
Ah, what's up? What'd you see?
I got this.
She just jumped.
In mid-air.
What the?
Catch!
Stop immediately!
Forget about them! We must go!
The whale forest has been invaded.
Talking animals?
There's a mink tribe.
Hey, I know those clothes.
But that's not Nami.
Damn, what the hell is that weapon?
That thing gave me a serious shock.
There's an invader in the Will Force, too?
Yes, the situation is dire.
The Guardians are not going
to be happy about this.
What is she?
Some kind of dog? Listen,
you better tell us where you got that
outfit because it doesn't belong to you.
What did you do, Nutanami?
Do you think they're cannibals? Great!
No, I'm double scared!
Ah!
Oh, please don't eat me, nice lady!
Whoa, talk about air!
Man, do all of these mink
people have skills like that?
Carrot!
See anything unusual?
Over there!
I just hope we're not too late!
It's in the whale forest on
the other side of Karoo City!
I thought so.
Let's go, Warnie!
Now! Get on!
Right!
There's no time to transport you, Tia.
Listen closely.
All of you should head to the west,
by way of the right-trump forest.
And then, if you turn left at the
swamp, you'll reach right flank.
That's where you'll
find your cruise corpse.
We'll find what?!
Wait for us in right flank!
We'll catch up to you shortly!
I wonder if they're going to be okay.
That group was the Straw Hat Pirates.
Is that true?
They're in for a real shock.
We don't have time to
deal with them right now.
This is far more urgent.
Since the rest of the crew
has finally showed up,
I assume that the invader in the
Whale Forest is Straw Hat Luffy.
And while he may be their captain,
the Guardians won't show him any mercy.
The rest of the crew is dead!
Well, she did say that there was a
corpse, which means they weren't eaten.
That's not the point!
Stop being so morbid!
That's enough crying.
Nobody's been killed.
Curly Browse is with them, remember?
Yeah, Zorro's right.
There's no way they would
go down that easily.
Those animal ladies must be
trying to trick us somehow.
Probably so, but what a terrible lie.
Tell me, the rest of your crewmates,
they should be here, correct? Uh-huh.
And can you contact them?
I'm afraid not.
I didn't even really expect
I would see them again.
Actually, hold on.
Almost forgot.
I still have a Vever card.
See this?
It's for our navigator, Beppo.
Oh, yeah, the talking polar bear, right?
I guess he's a mink, isn't he?
Yeah, this place is where he was born.
However,
he left the island when
he was a little boy,
so he doesn't remember much about living
here or being part of the mink tribe.
I've known him for a whole decade.
He's a friend.
So if you want reliable info, follow me.
Wait, there's a town that way, you guys.
I remember seeing it from the tower.
I mean, who knows what we'll run into?
It's not safe!
We might see some cannibals.
It's better than trusting
what that dog lady said.
I think we should follow him.
Come on.
Gum-Gum!
Mugolaba!
What's wrong?
It doesn't make sense!
His Electro isn't working at all!
Wait, you two!
Please stop attacking him!
It's fine, he's somebody I know!
Either way, he's still an intruder!
If he won't stop, then I'm
afraid I'll have to force you...
...out of our way!
Oh, no!
Parshat Bart!
I don't think we can handle this guy.
You're right, he's way too tough.
Donnie, stop this! That's enough!
Look what I've got!
How about a banana?
Lucky me!
That's one way to do it.
Dog?
Yutia must be Straw Hat Luffy.
My name is Wanda,
and this is Carrot.
We'll do you no harm.
So don't resist.
This place is full of talking animals.
It's like a whole island full of choppers.
What's up with these two?
They came and jumped me for no reason.
That's because your kind is
forbidden to enter this area.
Whoa, back up.
Guardians, please.
Forget this man.
We'll take him.
Fine, for Wanda's sake.
Retreat, Roddy!
Be me!
It's Pedro.
Everyone, out!
I didn't even notice they were here!
Be grateful Yutia didn't encounter
them on a moonlit night. Strawhead!
Oh, come on!
Why do you look so confused?
Don't you remember us?
We took care of you after what
happened back in Marineford!
How could you forget that? Oh, yeah!
I know you!
You're the talking bear who was
part of Traffy's crew, right?
Who's Traffy?
Listen, our captain is the
genius surgeon Trafalgar Law!
We're the heart pirates, okay? I know.
That's what I said.
Don't start with me!
So, we've kept up with the news.
So much has been happening.
Guess we're allies now, huh?
Is our captain here? Uh-huh.
Jeffy's here with us.
You keep saying that name!
Who is that? Aye-aye!
That's what I call law.
Oh, really?
That wasn't clear.
Well, whatever, I'm just glad
to hear he's on the island.
Yeah, I can't wait to
see our captain again!
There's no doubting it.
This city was attacked.
Judging by the size, the population
could be in the hundreds of thousands.
But I don't see a single resident.
If we stay out here in the open,
they'll come and get us for sure!
They're probably still
around here, aren't they?
We gotta run for cover!
Let's hurry!
Is that some kind of torture device?
Kind of hard to say whether we're dealing
with humans or something else here
I don't know, but they're
all over the place.
Must be something pretty
strong to do that.
Hey, check this out.
I think it's some kind of footprint.
Another elephant, maybe?
Yeah, everything's bad.
I say we just...
There were claw marks, so it
could have been infighting.
We do know one thing.
This place fell, but it
hasn't been that long.
Two weeks, maybe less.
Wait, really?
If that's true, then this city got
wrecked while our friends were here!
Oh, so that's why there's nobody around.
The country's history
goes back for centuries.
It's called the Mokumo Dukedom.
It was only half a month ago that I
could still see everyone's smiling faces.
The name of the man who caused
all this suffering is Jack.
Whoa!
Now what's up?
Is this something bad?
Hooray! Inruption's coming!
I'm on the train!
Get a lorny!
We'll head to right flank!
Your friends are waiting there!
Oh sweet!
You mean Sanji's group, right?
Hello?